[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Did the 13 colonies declare their independence in 1776?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Elephants sometimes have stillborn births, but are not bothered by the loss since the baby was never alive.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie The Shawshank Redemption Andy Dufresne had a best friend in jail named Red. Why did they call him Red?", "correct_answer": "It was short for his last name.", "incorrect_answers": ["He had red hair.", "His favorite color was red.", "He had a horrible temper."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what country was the 2007 movie 300 filmed?", "correct_answer": "Canada", "incorrect_answers": ["New Zealand", "Australia", "U.S.A."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What country is generally regarded as the oldest republic in the world?", "correct_answer": "San Marino", "incorrect_answers": ["France", "Bulgaria", "Denmark"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What dog breed has an elongated body, very short legs, short shiny coat and a long snout?", "correct_answer": "Dachshund", "incorrect_answers": ["Dogo Guatemalteco", "English Foxhound", "Elo"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What two colors are featured on the flag and coat of arms of Malta, a country consisting of seven Mediterranean islands?", "correct_answer": "White and red", "incorrect_answers": ["Green and black", "Yellow and purple", "Blue and yellow"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who portrays the villain, Alexander Conklin in the 2002 movie The Bourne Identity?", "correct_answer": "Chris Cooper", "incorrect_answers": ["Brian Cox", "Gabriel Mann", "Clive Owen"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was Freddie Mercurys real name?", "correct_answer": "Farroukh Bulsara", "incorrect_answers": ["Frederick Von Messner", "Fernando Mercurio", "Fredricio de la Massino"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "During the Bonnie Situation act in Pulp Fiction, Vincent and Jules have to wear Jimmys clothes after they clean up.  What is the name of the school on Vincents t-shirt?", "correct_answer": "UC Santa Cruz", "incorrect_answers": ["UCLA", "UC Santa Barbara", "Berkeley"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "One of these statements about the enigmatic number 23 is wrong.", "correct_answer": "All statements are in fact true.", "incorrect_answers": ["Each parent contributes 23 chromosomes to the DNA of a child.", "Julius Caesar was stabbed 23 times when he was assassinated.", "The Knights Templar had 23 Grand Masters, the last being Jacques de Molay."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The cell has up to several thousands of these tiny organelles scattered in its cytoplasm. They are often called cellular power plants, because they convert organic materials into energy.", "correct_answer": "Mitochondria", "incorrect_answers": ["Vacuoles", "Chloroplasts", "Ribosomes"]}]